Theme park!
- It was so fun.
- I had a blast today.
- Yeah.
- It was really fun.
- Seung-hyun, why don't you agree?
- Huh?
- Did you not have fun?
- Of course, I did!
I'm so jealous of your Pingu bag.
HAN SU-JI
AN JEONG-EUN
- What a fun day.
- So funny.
It's so warm here.
But honestly, during today's date,
I couldn't look Hyuk-joon in the eyes.
You see, Tae-hoon was there too.
And I had no problem looking at Tae-hoon,
but looking Hyuk-joon in the eyes
was kind of scary.
I couldn't bring myself to do it.
In any case, that's a change for me
because I didn't feel anything
like that around Jung-yun.
That's why I said he's my top pick.
But why do I feel like this
when he's so not my type?
I'm in trouble. Hyuk-joon might be
my final pick at this rate.
- Really?
- It's her first time admitting it.
I came clean to Hyuk-joon about the gift.
- What about it?
- That I gave it to him.
A MOMENT AGO
So, did you get the gift?
The gift? Oh, so it was from you.
I was so confused.
- I actually thought it was from Han-ju.
- Oh, right.
Jin-woo told me he got a gift from you.
So I thought my gift couldn't be from you.
You'd usually give it to just one guy.
But I really appreciate it.
Hyuk-joon thinks
gift-giving is a big deal.
Yeah, he was actually a bit annoyed
that she gave a gift
- to both of them.
- He was furious.
He wasn't just a bit annoyed.
He was outraged.
- Gifts are really important to him.
- Yes.
DAY 8
D-2 UNTIL FINAL SELECTION
- There are only two days left.
- Oh my gosh.
There isn't much time left at all.
Let's go to the Noraebang.
Hyun-seo just keeps getting hurt.
She's feeling very frustrated.
You know how Hyuk-joon and I
went on a lot of dates at the start?
You went almost every day.
And then Hyuk-joon went
- on four three-way dates.
- Yeah, he did.
And yesterday, he said to me
that he had no idea
those other women were interested in him.
He said he wanted to give them a chance.
What? He said what?
Wait. Let me get this straight.
So when I heard that,
I was like, "What?"
And on the three-way dates,
I found out for the first time
that other women were interested in me.
And I felt like it wasn't fair
to rule them out completely,
- so, I--
- What?
You were doing it for them?
It's hard to understand him.
That's what I'm saying.
- But I think--
- He must have really thought that.
He must have thought it at least once,
which is why he said it.
We don't just blurt out things
we've never thought about.
We don't say things out of nowhere.
I think his popularity
has kind of gone to his head.
Go and tell him right now
to pick you
if there's a one-on-one date today.
- That's twisting his arm.
- That's true.
Whatever he chooses… This is how I see it.
It's not like we are already a couple.
No, you're not.
We're still getting to know each other.
So I don't want to force him
to do what I want.
If he goes
on a date with someone else again today,
I'll just move on and be done with it.
This really is the last chance.
What if he doesn't
pick Hyun-seo again today?
Oh, Hyuk-joon.
Please choose wisely today.
- We got a text.
- What is it?
- They got a text.
- Yeah.
"You will go on a secret date today."
"You will get a guaranteed one-on-one date
with the person you pick."
A GUARANTEED DATE
WITH ONE PERSON OF YOUR CHOICE
- What?
- Oh, come on!
Can we not pick anyone?
"You don't need to pick anyone."
YOU DON'T NEED TO PICK ANYONE
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO GO ON A DATE
I did hesitate a bit.
It's hard knowing
it doesn't have to be mutual.
- The person I pick might not pick me.
- Right.
I need to do it anyway.
I didn't feel conflicted anymore.
In terms of my feelings,
I've pretty much made up my mind.
So I felt like I had to go on a date
with this person.
That's why I chose her.
For the first time,
we were allowed
to choose not to go on a date.
I gave it a lot of thought.
Wow.
Whoever they go on a date with
will be a secret to everyone else.
And they get a guaranteed
one-on-one date with their pick.
- It's an amazing chance.
- It's a great opportunity.
But Hyuk-joon said
he is sure of his feelings
for the first time.
Who do you think he picked?
I think it's Hyun-seo.
- Hyun-seo?
- Yes.
When he spoke to her,
he remembered how cool she is.
- Right.
- He suddenly remembered.
But Su-ji's a possibility too, right?
Su-ji said she couldn't
look Hyuk-joon in the eye.
And Hyuk-joon must have felt
that kind of romantic tension too.
- Maybe.
- You're right.
I think he could pick Su-ji.
- Where is this? It's pretty.
- It looks like a pottery studio.
It's perfect for Su-ji.
- Oh, it's Jae-seo.
- Jae-seo!
- There's only one person he would pick.
- No doubt about it.
- Hello.
Don't you think
whenever you go on a date with me,
it's a weird activity?
Oh, you're right.
You knew I would pick you, didn't you?
Oh, I picked you too.
Really?
- What?
- Huh?
Yeah.
- What?
- What's going on?
- Seo-yoon picked him?
- She picked him too?
- All of a sudden?
- I've suddenly got butterflies.
- What's going on?
I've wanted to say something
to him since yesterday,
and I felt I had to say it today.
So I picked Jae-seo without hesitation.
How great. They picked each other.
Oh, how great!
- Jae-seo's heart must be racing.
- Yeah.
Did you go to the Post Office yesterday?
No, I did think about it, but…
Did you?
Yeah, I did.
- Really?
- Yeah, and I wrote you
a letter saying I wanted to talk today.
- Did you?
- Yes. I wrote you a letter,
and you seemed a bit under the weather,
so I also bought you some vitamins.
Oh, thank you.
Make sure to take them.
What on earth?
It took nine days
for her to show some interest back.
Really? Hang on.
LAST NIGHT
Dear. Jae-seo…
I wrote in the letter,
"Let's definitely talk tomorrow."
And he seemed a bit unwell,
so I also got him some vitamins.
So even if we didn't get
a one-on-one date today,
I would have still found
a way to talk to you.
Well…
Honestly, I don't really think
my feelings will change.
I don't mean just toward you,
but all the guys here.
I don't think I feel
romantically attracted to anyone.
Right.
Given how
I don't feel that kind
of attraction toward anyone
even when I'm
in a special set-up like this,
maybe I'm just not someone
who gets those kinds of feelings.
For me to keep spending time
worrying about this
and spend the rest of my time here
not being myself…
The weather's too nice for that,
and there are so many great sights.
So I plan to just enjoy
the rest of my time here.
Okay.
Oh, this is…
- Thanks for telling me.
- No problem.
I think
it makes perfect sense.
Because we live in a world
where we can be perfectly content
without being in a relationship.
- Right.
- So…
I don't think it's a problem.
Thanks for saying that.
Honestly, as I've grown
closer to Seo-yoon recently,
my feelings have slowly grown
just naturally being around her.
But she told me very clearly
that she wasn't interested,
so now I…
I guess I need to start moving on.
That's where I'm at now.
Will something like this
ever happen again?
I feel like it is
a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
I even wondered
if I deserved to be this happy,
and I don't have any regrets.
Even if I were to go back
to day one with this knowledge,
I would still pick Seo-yoon.
Oh my gosh.
I admire how he is
so in touch with his emotions.
Yeah.
It's so great how grounded Jae-seo is.
- Yes.
- He was very cool just now.
Yeah, it's such a shame.
If only he had been just as laid-back
when he talked with her earlier,
perhaps things would've
panned out differently.
He said that he would pick her again
even though it's been hard
and things didn't work out.
It's just so cool.
- He really is a sexy guy.
- Yes.
Kudos to you, Jae-seo!
Where is this?
Oh, I think it's a batting cage.
- I think it's Soo-hyun.
- I think it's her.
It is her!
How will things go
for the Blueberry Couple today?
- Tae-hoon?
- It must be him, right?
Is it Tae-hoon? Who is it?
It must be Tae-hoon.
- It's Hoon-tae.
- I knew it.
- "Hoon-tae"?
- It's him.
She's happy to see him.
- Welcome.
- She's in a good mood today.
- Hello.
SECRET DATE
SOO-HYUN, TAE-HOON
- How does this work?
- I'm not sure.
This pair is also…
- They're moving at different paces.
- They're a bit out of sync.
- It's a bit touch and go.
- They need to talk it out.
What should we do?
We need to make a bet.
- Sure.
- That goes without saying.
What shall we bet on?
How many coupons do you have left?
- I have three.
- Three?
Then, I'd better take one.
- Okay!
- I want to get a gift of my choice.
What about you?
What do you want to play for?
Make me the same thing you made today.
The strawberry banana smoothie? Okay.
Tae-hoon's a smoothie wizard.
- He's a fruit expert.
- "Smoothie wizard."
I found this hard.
I don't get how to do this.
I can't do it.
She hasn't gotten a single hit.
It can be so embarrassing
- when the guy you like is watching.
- Yeah.
It's embarrassing for guys too.
I've definitely lost.
- This is great.
- Oh, man.
I'm going to count.
I'm ready.
I'll win no matter what.
He has great form.
- I think he'll do well.
- It looks promising.
He's good.
You've done this before, right?
- Right?
- No.
Seems like he has.
- He's got some experience.
- Oh, come on.
Soo-hyun looks impressed.
You must really want those vitamins.
She's got butterflies.
- Look at her. She's hiding her smile.
- You're right.
My smoothie…
- The smoothie store's closing.
- Oh, no. Why?
- He won't make any more for her?
- Score!
He says he's quitting.
He said he won't make her
any more smoothies.
- Wanna drink something?
- Yeah.
What do you want to drink?
Oh, are you buying?
Aren't we going Dutch?
This one? Jetty?
- Got it.
- Pass it over.
We should have bet on this.
No way.
What a dopamine rush.
One of my three coupons…
You have to be ruthless
when it comes to things like this.
I can't just let you win.
You'll get spoiled.
I've given you an honorable reason
to use the coupon.
I…
Darn it. I can't even speak.
Oh, man.
So did you pick me? Or…
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
Oh, they don't know
whether they picked each other mutually.
I don't know. Why?
Why did you request… Who are you?
- What?
- Huh?
"Who are you?"
Oh, he didn't pick her.
SOO-HYUN REQUESTED THE DATE
So you might have another date later.
- Me? Maybe.
- Yeah.
What's wrong with him?
His tone could be a little hurtful.
Judging by how Soo-hyun's looking unhappy…
Did you check it?
Check what?
- Your cabinet.
- No, I didn't.
I haven't looked.
Did you put something in it?
You didn't check it?
Did you put something in there?
Okay. So whatever's in there is from you.
- You haven't looked at all?
- No.
What?
TWO DAYS AGO
I worked up a lot of courage
to write him a letter.
I said that I enjoyed the one-on-one date
and that I hoped we would get
another one-on-one date.
All right. Here you go.
It's been two whole days.
If he was interested in her,
he would have checked it.
- Yes.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- She must be upset.
You said you went regularly!
I haven't been once
since I… Because I'm done using it.
Honestly, after I put it in your cabinet,
I kept watching to see how you reacted,
but you didn't show any reaction at all.
And you seemed
like you had a lot on your mind.
So I wasn't sure if you saw it or not.
I wanted to ask you,
but I couldn't find you.
Why do you keep looking for me?
Stop looking.
I won't be going today, either.
What?
Why won't he go
when she told him she left something?
I'm starting to get a bit annoyed.
Why not?
Because I'm not using it right now.
But you might have gotten something.
Gotten something?
I don't plan to go at all.
Then you'll never know
if I'll give you the vitamins or not.
Put them in my cabinet and then tell me.
Why is he taking it this far?
Unfortunately, even though
I haven't read the letter yet,
I know who it's from,
and I have some idea
of what it's probably about.
But on my part,
in terms of romantic attraction,
I'm not as attracted
to Soo-hyun as she is to me.
So I'm trying to tell her indirectly
that her interest in me
is making me a bit uncomfortable.
Oh, come on.
You can't do that.
Tae-hoon's being so rude right now.
- That's an awful attitude.
- Yeah.
He's being really rude.
- This is…
- "Rude."
It's rude.
- Don't you think so?
- It is a bit rude.
- He's being such a rude guy.
- It's…
It's just as In-guk said.
- He summed it up nicely.
- Yeah, an awful attitude.
- It is.
- Totally awful.
He knows how she feels.
- That's what makes it so bad.
- Yeah.
- He knows she requested this date.
- Exactly.
And this is how he behaves?
In Seo-yoon's case,
she was honest and straightforward.
- Yes.
- That's why Jae-seo
- was able to take it so calmly.
- Yes.
- But the way Tae-hoon is acting right now…
- Yeah.
- It's hurtful.
- It is.
She must be wondering,
"How do I take this?"
- Yeah.
- It's just offensive.
The fact that he keeps smiling
makes it even worse.
- Exactly!
- Yes.
The way he's smiling
is bound to make her wonder,
"Is he kidding or is he messing me about?"
Exactly.
When I'm the one talking, it means
the participants aren't being problematic.
But if In-guk or Han-na speak up,
- it means they're doing terribly.
- It means it's serious.
When I'm the one talking,
you can assume it's not so bad.
Do you not feel any…
Do you not have any concerns?
I did have one concern.
What was it?
Right now, I feel…
- Something's changed?
- There has been
- a slight change.
- Slight?
My feelings have changed a bit.
I'm not sure what to do.
I see.
It feels like Tae-hoon's changed a bit.
A lot, actually.
Do you think it might change?
- Me?
- Yeah.
You mean my top pick?
I'm talking to her right now.
- I'm talking to her.
- I'm very satisfied.
I don't know.
When I was talking to Tae-hoon,
something felt a bit off.
But I can't put my finger on exactly what.
And I told him that I wrote him a letter,
but he said he hadn't seen it yet.
It made me wonder.
Does he just never go to the Post Office
or is he just not interested?
I felt upset for various reasons.
Of course, she did.
I'll see you back at the village.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Oh, dear.
It must be her first time
experiencing something like this.
- She must be taken aback. It's so sudden.
- Exactly.
- She hardly asked him out or proposed.
- My point exactly.
She hasn't pushed him for anything.
But Tae-hoon's suddenly being
too mean to my Soo-hyun.
She's the participant
I'm rooting for the most this season.
I was rooting
for the Blueberry Couple too.
It can feel a bit much for Tae-hoon
because she's acting like his girlfriend
and giving him so much attention.
- It might feel a bit early for that.
- Yeah.
That said,
instead of going about it
in such a hurtful way,
- it would've been nicer to just be honest.
- Exactly.
This is not good.
My heart breaks for her.
Yeah, I'm worried she'll blame herself
- and wonder if she did something wrong.
- Exactly.
- Who's that?
- What?
- Was Soo-hyun picked
- It's another date.
- by someone else?
- Someone's coming.
Who is it?
Seung-hyun?
- It's Seung-hyun!
- Oh, is it you, Seung-hyun?
- Hi.
- Hello, sir.
Oh my.
Well done.
- This is great.
- I love it.
Didn't Seung-hyun pick her
for the first impression vote?
They were the only people
who picked each other.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Seung-hyun requested it.
You got here first.
Yeah, I just… Yeah.
- You just got here?
- Yeah.
I was so surprised.
Seung-hyun hasn't
spoken to me much at all.
So when he showed up,
I was amazed and surprised
to get a chance to talk to him.
SECRET DATE
SEUNG-HYUN, SOO-HYUN
- So…
- Yeah?
I can't believe how nervous I am.
Well, Su-ji was my top pick.
And I was a bit upset
when she rejected me.
You asked if I thought my feelings for you
might grow over time.
- Do you remember?
- Yeah.
I think that's unlikely.
My mind's made up now.
They don't suit each other.
But after a few days,
I started realizing it wasn't a big deal.
And I thought I should pick
who I'm most interested in right now,
and Soo-hyun is the closest
to my ideal type, looks-wise.
Good thinking!
Honestly, I kind of…
I kind of want to talk
to Soo-hyun a bit more
- if I get the chance.
- Then, go get her.
But
things are going well
between her and Tae-hoon.
Just go for it.
What's there to be scared of?
We're here to throw caution to the wind.
- Did we?
- She's right.
- Yes.
- Well-said, Hyun-seo.
I want to talk to Soo-hyun a bit more.
Is that okay?
- You don't mind?
- No, I don't.
Who the heck is that?
Jeez.
- Such weird sunglasses too.
- So weird.
- What the heck?
- Why bother getting his permission?
I thought to myself,
"Why didn't I do this before?"
I don't want any regrets,
so I wanted to talk to her
one-on-one before we left.
- It's our first time talking like this.
- Yeah, it is.
I actually wanted
to talk to you like this,
but the chance never came.
And to be honest,
I did think of trying to create a chance,
but I couldn't work up the courage.
I see.
So I feel lucky
that I got this chance today.
- I can't believe this took us so long.
- Yeah.
He's mentioned her consistently!
They suit each other.
Did I tell you this?
What?
I picked you
for the first impression vote.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I picked you too.
- Really?
You did? I had no idea.
Well, we haven't had a chance
to talk properly since then.
- Yes.
- That's right.
They picked each other.
But they didn't know!
It's day eight,
and they're only just finding out.
It took them eight days.
What a dramatic turn.
- Gosh.
- Straight away on their first proper date…
They must suddenly feel a bit giddy.
- So…
- Yeah?
What? What is it?
- Never mind.
- What?
What is it?
I felt I should check how Soo-hyun felt
before I expressed my feelings to her.
But I think I lacked the courage to ask.
It was nerve-racking
- talking to someone I'm interested in.
- Oh my.
This is great.
It's interesting that we're out here
- talking like this.
- Yeah.
But honestly, I feel a bit regretful.
- About what?
- I wanted
to work up the courage to say to you,
"Hey, do you want to talk?"
You should have.
Weren't we always
kind of around each other?
We were, but…
I felt like…
If I said, "Hey, let's go and talk,"
it would be a bit…
- Everyone would tease.
- Yeah, and the idea of that happening
- just made me so shy.
- Right.
Actually, I get that.
- What?
- Going up to someone and asking to talk
- isn't easy.
- No, it's not.
It's hard to be brave.
They seem at ease.
They look good together.
It's so nice to see.
And writing a letter is a bit…
- It feels a bit cheesy.
- Why not write a letter?
- I checked my cabinet so often.
- Really?
- Yeah. It's fine to write a letter.
- Yeah?
What's wrong with it?
When I talk to someone,
it's not that I feel
awkward or uncomfortable,
- but since I don't know them well,
- Yeah.
I don't know how to start a conversation,
and I'm worried I'll make a mistake.
- What kind of mistake?
- For example,
what if I accidentally
say something that bothers them?
But in any case,
- we are, you know, talking right now.
- Yeah.
And I feel like
you don't need to worry about that.
You shouldn't worry, and honestly…
During my makeover…
We can talk about this now, right?
They taught me
how to be better at conversations
and stuff like that.
And my speech teacher taught me
about how to handle the fear
of how the other person will react.
They said it's unlikely
the other person will be insulted
as long as you express yourself clearly.
And since it's unlikely,
you shouldn't worry too much
about if you're being rude
- and just ask them.
- Really?
Even outside of this show,
you might keep
facing this problem in the future,
so I think it would be good
for you to be less hesitant.
Am I getting a makeover right now?
That's not what I'm trying to do.
- Are you?
- I just mean if that was your concern…
I just wanted
to share the advice I received.
I'm touched.
You know, I think
- that's a good way to think about it.
- Yeah.
Wow. This is so great.
What perfect timing.
- Soo-hyun was a little hurt.
- Yes, she was.
- So it's--
- It's great timing.
It really could be the perfect timing.
Speaking as a member
of Soo-hyun's fan club--
- You're in her fan club?
- Since when?
- You're her fan?
- You didn't know, did you?
- No, we didn't.
- See here?
You're a fanboy at heart?
When she first matched with Tae-hoon,
she was excited that he picked her,
so she spoke a mile a minute.
But right now,
she's not talking too fast.
- She's calm.
- She's having a proper conversation
- Yes.
- with Seung-hyun.
I bet they're currently dating.
They even have the same initials!
They're both SH.
They can get matching initial necklaces.
- Yes.
- You know the ones.
They can get SH stickers
on the back of their cars.
So, by any chance…
Have you made up your mind yet?
I thought my mind was
pretty much made up, but…
But something's changed?
Yeah, it's changed a bit.
I feel like I need
to give it some more thought.
We need to explore all options.
Yeah.
- Let's do this.
- Let's do it.
- Wow.
- Gosh.
- Good. Let's go, SH.
- She just got butterflies.
I feel like I've gotten used
to how things are here.
- So--
- Me too. You seem very well-adapted.
- Do I?
- Yeah.
Your "mingle, single" on day one…
- Oh, "Are you single? Let's mingle"?
- That dad joke.
To be honest, Car, the garden
made me tell that joke.
Did you ever use it again?
- I mean--
- Huh? Should I use it on you now?
- Are you going to?
- Right now?
- Go on.
- Show her.
Are you from Tasy?
What?
The land of fantasy.
Success. That worked.
It worked, didn't it?
- What do you think? Not bad, right?
- Don't do it again.
Throw that joke book away.
Why would you…
- She told him to throw it away.
- She laughed.
She enjoyed it. She's laughing.
- It totally won her heart.
- It's like…
- It totally worked on her.
- It's like this.
When she gets home, she'll think,
- "That was so stupid." But then…
- Yes.
You get what I mean, right?
- You get it!
- The more you think about it,
- the funnier it gets.
- It grows on you.
- Yeah.
- "Are you from Tasy?"
"The land of fantasy."
Throw that joke book away.
Why would you…
I read it this morning.
Tell her a few more.
- I thought, "This one's quite good."
- What's good about it?
What are you talking about?
Seung-hyun is good at keeping
the conversation going,
and he's quite encouraging.
Even though I was bad at baseball,
he kept telling me I was doing a good job.
I haven't hit a single one.
But it was a good effort!
- Look, don't clap.
- Okay, I won't.
- I'll just stay still.
- I've missed them all.
I thought, "I should have talked
to him sooner."
I found him more fun than I thought.
This warms my heart.
Seung-hyun is so charming.
He's way better than Tae-hoon,
who only cared about winning.
- He is. Seriously.
- Yeah.
Tae-hoon was acting like
he was on Physical: 100.
At first, it seemed like Seung-hyun was
just on this show to have fun.
- But he's being so sincere to Soo-hyun.
- Yeah.
His intentions seem so pure.
- He's turned into a cool guy.
- He has.
- They seem so compatible.
- They are.
I hope things work out between them.
- Me too.
- Same.
Also, they're based in similar regions.
If not, just move, Seung-hyun.
I'll find you a place!
- Who's this?
- Who is it?
- Su-ji.
- It's Su-ji.
Why does she look so deeply troubled?
Su-ji, you look like
you have a lot on your mind.
Is it Hyuk-joon?
- Or Jung-yun?
- Is it Jung-yun?
Could it be Hyuk-joon?
- Who is it?
- Hyuk-joon? Based on those long strides…
Hey.
- Hello.
- It's Jung-yun.
Want to sit?
I wanted to spend
a bit more time with Su-ji.
So I picked her for the date.
Yesterday,
Hyuk-joon and Jung-yun's ranks changed,
so I said Hyuk-joon
became my top pick.
Maybe because of that change,
I felt a bit conflicted.
And I just wanted to leave it up to fate.
But Jung-yun requested a date,
so I went to meet him.
Aren't you cold?
Not right now.
I guess Su-ji didn't pick him.
SECRET DATE
JUNG-YUN, SU-JI
This must be the place.
What's all this?
Hello.
You'll be making Japanese sweets today.
It's very similar to clay.
This should be fun.
This must be second nature to you.
Well…
Su-ji is a ceramicist, after all.
Hey, you're really good at this.
You should get into pottery.
You're doing well yourself too.
You might be better at this than me.
Do you want to date someone
who's like a friend
or someone who makes you
nervous and excited?
This is her dilemma right now.
It's so obviously about him and Hyuk-joon.
I said that I wanted a partner
who is like a friend.
In my diary in the 5 Minute Library,
for the question about dating
someone older, younger, or the same age--
Yeah, I noticed that you gave
a very detailed answer for each one.
You clearly gave it a lot of thought.
THEY'RE THE SAME AGE
BOTH WERE BORN IN 2000
That's why I said I prefer
someone of the same age.
What about you?
What will she say?
I think you need to feel butterflies.
You know, feeling nervous and stuff.
Because for me…
Have I told you this?
The last time I really liked someone
was in sixth grade.
Really?
I was head over heels for him.
So I got really nervous around him,
and I used to turn bright red.
My heart used to pound so hard.
So that feeling of being nervous and giddy
and wanting to impress the other person
became my idea of love.
- Jung-yun must get what she's getting at.
- Don't you think he caught on?
- I think he did.
- He's surprisingly perceptive.
Sixth grade… That's quite a long time ago.
A long time ago.
But it was such a major event in my life.
Sometimes, I feel like
I'm still stuck in that memory.
So…
I keep comparing everything to that.
Now that there isn't much time left,
if you feel like
your mind is basically made up,
will you express it
in one way or another?
Yeah, I think so.
- I'd have to let the other person know.
- Yeah.
Honestly, I want to run away from it all
since it's so uncomfortable.
But then my life will be
the same as before.
So I don't want to do that.
Sorry that I'm so…
- Why are you apologizing?
- I wish I could give you a clear answer.
I'm always so wishy-washy.
It is a little upsetting
since she's one of the women
I've talked to the most,
and we've spent a lot of time together,
but she's still unsure.
She hasn't made her mind up yet,
and she told me that directly.
And it doesn't feel like
there have been any big changes.
I feel like there's a bit of a wall.
There's an invisible wall between us.
And I hoped
to get a gift
or a letter or something like that.
Just in case I got anything,
I kept dropping by the Post Office, but…
Of course, there isn't anything.
I haven't gotten anything.
Oh, dear.
- The way he said that…
- Yeah.
Of course, it's empty.
I thought it would be nice
to get something from Su-ji.
He checked almost every day.
THIS MORNING
- He checked a lot but expected nothing.
- The way he said, "Of course, it's empty."
At the end of the day,
over the course of ten days,
I had to express my feelings
by working up courage.
And I had to wait for a reaction.
So, I…
expressed my feelings
and am waiting for a response.
I do feel a bit…
It is a bit tiring.
But
feeling conflicted
and having so much on your mind
is toughest on the person
going through it.
So all I can do is wait and see.
It's so heartbreaking.
- Yeah.
- The fact that he said to himself,
- "Of course, it's empty."
- Exactly.
He got his hopes up, and that was his way
- of comforting himself.
- Yeah.
But given the way Su-ji's acting,
- it doesn't seem like she cut him off.
- No.
I wonder what she's thinking.
Is she still interested in him,
or does she feel too bad
to reject him? It's hard to tell.
Who's this?
- Jin-woo.
- It's Jin-woo.
- He probably picked Jeong-eun.
- Yes.
I think so too. But maybe not?
It must be Jeong-eun, right?
Hi.
It's an outdoor date.
It is Jeong-eun.
JIN-WOO REQUESTED THE DATE
- Jin-woo requested it.
- You must be cold.
- It's a big spread.
- Right?
- I didn't expect it to be so fancy.
- Yeah.
It looks so tasty now that it's cooked.
Let's give it a taste.
- Thanks for grilling.
- Sure.
- Careful. It's hot.
- Okay.
- A camping date is so romantic.
- Yeah.
It's good.
We're seeing each other a lot.
It feels like I see you every day.
- We really don't have much time left.
- Right.
- Tomorrow's basically the last day.
- It is.
Are things going as you hoped?
- Lately, I feel a bit…
- You're not too sure?
Yeah.
- It's not about you.
- Right.
I just feel a bit confused
about my own mind.
- Jeong-eun was against dating a student.
- That's right.
- Oh, that's right.
- She had crossed it off, but…
- She had practical concerns.
- That's right.
- It makes sense she's conflicted.
- Yeah.
You do seem like
you have a lot on your mind.
But you feel quite sure
about your feelings, right?
- Yeah, I feel pretty sure.
- Right?
So…
I don't have any concerns left.
And I envy that.
When you have a lot of concerns,
it makes you hesitant.
But now that my mind's made up,
even if I feel
a bit anxious about something,
I'm like, "Let's just give it a try.
If it doesn't work out, oh well."
I really appreciate that you are
willing to give me a chance,
but I don't want you
to feel too pressured.
Here's what I think.
When you tell someone you like them,
on the surface,
it can seem like it's for them,
but I think it's actually
a little bit selfish.
You do it because it makes you happy.
Of course, it'd be great if it's mutual.
I do hope you will like me back.
But I appreciate you just hearing me out.
So don't feel too pressured.
Don't feel too…
You shouldn't worry
too much about it.
Just enjoy yourself.
It's so sweet of Jin-woo
to relieve the pressure.
Yeah, it's important to know
when to slow down.
To be honest,
I obviously wish
she would feel the same way.
I wish she was as sure as I am.
But she seems like the type
who takes time to make up her mind.
It's a shame that she seems
to be going back and forth.
It's like she's being
reluctantly pulled along.
Deep down,
I was a bit disappointed.
I definitely like him
a lot more as a person,
but I don't know
if my feelings are romantic.
Jin-woo's always been honest
about his interest in me.
I obviously appreciate that,
and it's a nice feeling.
But I feel like a student
and a working professional
have too many different values,
and I got the sense
that it would be hard to overcome that
if we actually got together.
And my feelings for him
aren't strong enough to give it a go.
That changes things, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
- It must be a big blocker for her.
Him being a student
and her being a working professional.
And her feelings for him
aren't strong enough to give it a shot
despite their differences.
- She's not that into him.
- Not enough to look past it.
Both Jeong-eun and Su-ji
need to make up their minds now
- and clearly express where they stand.
- Right.
Whose date is this?
Who is it?
Who's this?
- Han-ju.
- It's Han-ju!
I was a bit torn.
HAN-JU'S THREE-WAY DATE
I've only been interested
in you two from the start.
She picked Jin-woo and Hyuk-joon.
It must be one of them.
Looks-wise, her top pick
has always been Jin-woo.
Jin-woo? Oh, Han-ju? Hyuk-joon?
Who did she choose?
I wanted to talk
about different things with each of them.
So it was hard to choose.
- Hello.
- Hi.
SECRET DATE
HYUK-JOON, HAN-JU
She picked Hyuk-joon.
Hyuk-joon said he was
talking to several women
to get to know them.
But I figured his mind
must be made up by now,
so I requested a date with him
to ask him where he stands.
SECRET DATE
HAN-JU REQUESTED THE DATE
Did you expect this?
- A little bit.
- You had an inkling?
What did you…
Did you come straight from the village?
It's a secret.
So you did.
Oh, man. This is…
I feel like you may have done
the rounds today.
Not at all.
It's not like I can ask
since it's a secret.
She must be curious
if he's made up his mind or not.
That's why she requested the date,
so go on. Ask him.
So what's the latest?
You've spoken to most of the women now,
like you had planned.
Have you made up your mind?
My mind is…
Yeah, I think I've decided.
My mind is pretty much made up.
I don't know if it's okay
to ask this so directly,
but it's not me, is it?
Wow, coming in hot.
I think I'll feel better knowing.
I have an inkling,
but I'd feel better if I knew for sure.
- They need to decide today.
- They do.
- That's right.
- It's time.
You don't need to answer
if it's uncomfortable.
No, I need to be honest
about these things.
It makes sense that you want to know.
It is someone else.
I think I like someone else.
I do like someone else.
At least, Hyuk-joon's being honest
without leading her on.
That said…
You made the first move to talk to me,
and you were so honest with me
during the ten-minute rotation date.
And your honesty
really made me
feel drawn to you.
I admired your honesty,
and I'm attracted to honest people.
Right.
You took the initiative…
And I really enjoyed our date yesterday.
Yeah.
I enjoyed all our conversations too.
Gosh, you're so honest.
Well, actually…
I've never been good
at opening up about my feelings,
so I don't know how honest
I'm supposed to be.
It's making me lay out all my cards
on the table.
It has been
a bit challenging and tough.
But I came on this show
to try to open up more.
That's why I applied.
So I'm trying my best
even though it's embarrassing.
Thank you.
You're so admirable.
I felt like being clear and honest
was the respectful thing to do.
If I gave her a wishy-washy answer,
she would have to
just keep waiting around.
So I tried to be extra direct.
As soon as I walked in,
I got him to confirm
that his final selection
isn't going to be me.
I was a little embarrassed,
but I didn't really feel
disappointed or anything.
I would probably have been more hurt
if I'd had deeper feelings for him.
I'm just thankful that he made an effort
to get to know me. That's it.
- That's good.
- She's got high self-esteem.
Have a drink and move on.
I'm so curious what you girls talk about.
We share everything.
We really don't hold back.
Don't get upset
when you watch the show later.
- Did you badmouth me?
- Of course, we did.
You looked so savage just then.
I'm going to trash you so much
when I get back tonight.
You're in for it.
Talk smack all you want.
Trash him all night long.
- Han-ju sounds like her old self now.
- Yeah, it's nice to see.
They ended on a good note.
- Yeah.
- It's nice.
Hyuk-joon was so clear and upfront
about the fact
that she isn't the one for him,
so that closes the chapter on them.
And luckily, it seems
he's finally done doing the rounds.
- That's right.
- Yes.
Han-ju said she used to struggle
with being honest,
but she's really grown
during her time in the village.
Yes, it's nice to see.
Han-ju will meet her one true love.
I can see her in a gamjatang place
ordering gamjatang for one
and a bottle of soju,
when suddenly a man across the room
also orders gamjatang for one
and a bottle of soju.
- And their eyes meet.
- And the serving lady says,
"Oh, sorry, dear."
"You'll have to sit together."
- What a fun plot.
- That's exactly it!
So they'll shuffle to the same table.
But then they realize,
"Hey, you're that rude bastard."
- It's perfect.
- I can see it.
I really hope something like that
will happen for her.
Hyuk-joon's already waiting
for his next date.
Hyun-seo?
I feel like Hyun-seo and Hyuk-joon
might get into a fight.
- Oh, no.
- No!
- Don't do it!
- I can't watch this.
- Stop!
- Don't go on this date!
Don't do it.
- Don't go.
- I feel like this will be a disaster.
- I can't watch.
- Don't go on this date.
I wonder who requested it.
- Maybe Hyuk-joon?
- Did Hyuk-joon request it?
Or maybe Hyun-seo requested it
to set things straight?
Oh my gosh. I can't watch.
- Hello.
- Hi.
SECRET DATE
HYUK-JOON, HYUN-SEO
- It's so sunny out.
- Yeah.
Who did you pick today?
Me? Who do you think?
I'm not sure.
Well, I…
I just…
I got a letter requesting a date.
So I picked the person
who wrote the letter.
I see.
I wrote a letter yesterday.
Oh, look at them!
Good thing you read it.
Oh, he wrote her a letter.
THIS MORNING
I found a letter in my cabinet.
It was Hyuk-joon's handwriting.
He said he wanted to go
on a date with me today.
Since he took the initiative
to try to talk to me,
it made me think
I may have misunderstood him
by interpreting things only in my way.
And I wanted to ask him
exactly what he was thinking
when he said what he said.
So it was mutual?
They picked each other.
It's been a while
- since we…
- Sat face-to-face.
Yeah, just the two of us.
Obviously, we didn't know
how the dates would be decided today,
but if you were to pick
someone else again today,
I was going to just move on.
Really?
Because…
I don't know. To be honest…
You explained to me why
- you went on dates with other women.
- Yeah.
But your explanation
sounded a bit odd to me.
When you said
that you wanted to give a chance
to the women who were interested in you,
it made me raise my eyebrows a bit.
So, I wanted to ask
what exactly you meant by that.
Because it sounded to me like,
"I wasn't very interested in them,
but I gave it a go for their sake."
That's how it sounded to me.
It's hard to make sense of it.
Choose your words carefully, Hyuk-joon.
What I actually meant was
that during the three-way dates,
the other women told me
that they were interested in me,
and when I thought about it,
I realized I had never
properly talked to them one-on-one.
So, I wanted to talk to them.
They said they were interested,
but I hadn't even considered
trying to open up to them.
So I wanted to try.
That's why I talked to them.
So you wanted that chance for yourself?
- That's it, right?
- Yeah, I needed it for me.
That's right.
That's a much clearer explanation.
Does it make sense now?
Yes.
So you misspoke?
Yeah.
Is that really what he meant,
but he just worded it wrong?
I wondered why you
never tried to come and talk to me.
- Because…
- Yeah?
To be honest,
if I were being my usual self,
I would have gone to you first.
I think I would have gone to you
and told you I wanted to talk.
And I made my feelings so obvious,
but I felt like I had to always
take charge and go up to you first.
And at the same time,
it seemed like you had a lot on your mind.
- So…
- That part is true.
I thought you might feel pressured
if I asked to talk to you.
So I just waited,
but it was quite frustrating.
So I kept wondering
when you'd come and talk to me.
But I appreciated you
asking to talk yesterday.
And I'm glad to be
on this date with you today.
It felt like a load off my mind.
I was so frustrated before,
so I felt relieved.
What?
What on earth?
That's it? She just… She seems happy.
- How was your date yesterday?
- At the theme park?
- I had so much fun.
- It seemed like it.
You were like, "We had so much fun!"
And you were all wearing
those Pingu bags, so I got a bit jealous.
- He was jealous?
- I thought,
"Do I need to buy a Pingu bag too?"
- Buy one sneakily to join the crew.
- I was honestly a bit jealous.
- It was my idea.
- I know.
I guess you were bothered.
Of course, I was.
So today, I didn't hesitate
even for a second.
I picked you instantly.
And last night,
you looked pretty, so…
Really?
On my part, I used to have
a big weight on my mind
because I had hoped Hyun-seo
would express her feelings
a bit more directly.
You really didn't get anything?
Me?
I'm not sure.
- You're not sure?
- No.
- It's a secret.
- Oh, is it?
So, in that respect,
I did feel a bit upset.
I was also torn
over shared interests versus fate.
Then I realized that you can
enjoy activities even with your friends.
But someone being on your mind
and the feeling of missing them…
That feels like fate.
So you were sulking, Hyuk-joon?
I told you.
- That's it, right?
- He was upset.
Having similar hobbies and stuff
didn't matter, in the end.
He figured it out by doing the rounds.
- Hiking and whatnot didn't matter.
- Right.
What does this mean for Su-ji?
"I did the rounds,
and it turns out nothing beats fate."
Do you think
your mind is completely made up now?
I feel a bit embarrassed, but yeah.
Gosh, he's sure.
Good boy.
Since yesterday,
I've wanted to tell you,
"I did the rounds like you said,
and now I'm back."
I never told you to do the rounds.
You told me to talk to other women.
But did you need to go
on other dates to do that?
Yeah, she never told him to do the rounds.
Is there somewhere I can hide?
I just couldn't believe
that you wasted two chances
to pick me as your date.
It's honestly the first time in my life
I have ever waited for a guy.
You should be honored.
Of course, I am. It's a huge honor.
I'm not usually that kind of girl.
I'm honored.
- This is a thing.
- What's that?
It's an honor.
Where did you get that from?
Everyone kept saying, "Thank you,"
like that in the Noraebang.
They bowed like this.
Yeah.
- Seo-yoon started it.
- Oh, really?
"It's an honor."
- It's not quite playing hard-to-get, but…
- Right?
It's like when a friend
you haven't seen in a while
comes to you crying
and complains about her boyfriend.
So you cuss him out,
but then the next day,
she's like, "We're back together."
- That's what it's like.
- Yeah.
- She is giving off that kind of vibe.
- Yeah, she is.
We were all a bit taken aback
because he was too attached
to Hyun-seo from the start.
- Right, but he turned cold overnight.
- That's right.
I think he just chose his words wrong.
When I asked him about it today,
he confirmed that he did
develop an interest in the others,
and he wanted to give himself
a chance to get to know them.
It's not that I completely understand,
but I feel like he confirmed
his feelings for me on today's date.
So, I'll try to be
a bit less skeptical from now on.
Judging by their faces,
it seems they've cleared the air.
As long as Hyun-seo's happy.
- That's all that matters.
- Yeah, exactly.
Just leave them be.
They're happy, so leave them be.
And to be honest,
I don't remember much else
other than him complimenting me
on how I styled myself yesterday.
That was the most memorable moment.
Forget everything else.
There's nothing better
than being told you're pretty.
Hyun-seo is…
Just as I sensed from the start,
her overall vibe is
the type of vibe I find attractive.
I've realized she is exactly my type.
As for our date, just as I had expected,
I felt butterflies,
and I got excited when our eyes met.
I was sad the time passed so quickly.
He's really back to his old self.
The stairs are slippery, so be careful.
Okay.
- I feel like our outfits match.
- Do they?
We're both wearing a coat over a sweater.
- Uh oh.
- And we're both in black.
- You're right.
- They nearly held hands.
- Similar color tones and everything.
- Yeah.
- And it's not like we planned it.
- Right.
Hyun-seo should've grabbed his hand.
Just go for it?
And maybe Su-ji knows by now too.
Now that Hyuk-joon's requested
a date with someone else,
she'll figure out where he stands.
- So, what will Su-ji do now?
- Right.
- And what will Soo-hyun do?
- Exactly.
- That's the question.
- Let's keep watching.
Time is really running out now.
Seo-yoon.
Hey! You're back!
Yeah.
- This is--
- What do I do?
What's wrong?
- I think I'm going to cry.
- Why?
Why?
What's wrong, Soo-hyun?
I don't know.
Don't cry.
I'll give you a hug.
Who made you cry?
- Oh my gosh.
- Come here.
Don't cry.
On the date…
What is it?
- Don't cry.
- I don't know…
It's okay.
You're okay.
Lean on me until you're all cried out.
Don't cry.
I was quite upset.
I thought he would have picked me.
But he suddenly acted
like he had another date lined up
to get to know someone else.
That's why I felt troubled.
To be honest, I went
to give him the vitamins earlier.
- Don't tell me…
- Oh, because she lost the bet.
Those gummy vitamins are tasty.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
But what if he still hasn't
taken the letter I left yesterday?
No way.
Take a look.
- Can I open someone else's cabinet?
- Yeah.
It's still in here.
Why won't he take it?
- Unbelievable. This is…
- That's so harsh.
Take it, Tae-hoon.
A letter is such a heartfelt gift.
How could he?
I did consider taking it back out,
but I'd already given it
and I already told him about it,
so he'd be flustered if it's gone.
Hang on.
Yeah.
Oh, man. I wasn't going to cry.
Hold on. This is driving me crazy.
I'm sorry. I need a minute.
Okay. I'll keep going.
Yeah.
Don't cry.
I'm trying my best to understand.
Maybe Tae-hoon was busy.
I'm trying to convince myself.
Busy doing what?
Right?
Oh, Soo-hyun. Don't cry.
Are you reading a book?
She told me she wrote a letter.
But she said she would
also buy me vitamins,
and I felt too lazy
to go to the Post Office twice.
So I gave her time to add the vitamins.
Stop smiling.
His smile makes you even more…
What's making me so mad…
- It makes you angrier.
- His smile is so unnatural.
He'll make a comment and then be like…
- That's right.
- He smiles after a beat.
"I gave her time."
This is what's so infuriating!
He's making me so angry.
It's Seung-hyun.
- Where are you going?
- Go!
- Where are you off to?
- Go to her!
- Please.
- Now's the time.
Let's go, SH!
Come on, SH couple!
Go quickly!
NORAEBANG
I'm going to check out how I look.
Pull her aside!
- Where are you going?
- To look in the bathroom mirror…
- The bathroom?
- Yeah. Why?
- What's up?
- I wanted a quick chat.
- Okay.
- You don't mind?
Well done.
That's the stuff.
- Well done, Seung-hyun!
- Way to go!
- He's shy.
- He's so shy right now.
He's feeling bashful.
I'm not sure what to say. One sec.
I called you out, but…
No, it's okay. I'm enjoying the fresh air.
- The fresh air?
- Yeah.
I needed to cool off.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Honestly, at the start… Well…
- Yeah?
- You know I kept having dates with Su-ji?
- Yeah.
After those dates,
I started to really develop
deep feelings for her.
- For Su-ji?
- Yeah.
But then…
She said she appreciated it
- but felt we were on different pages.
- It wasn't mutual.
- She said that?
- That's what she said.
- It kind of hurt.
- Of course!
- Of course, it hurt. You're only human.
- Yeah.
- So, it hurt.
But after time passed,
I felt… I feel better.
So…
As I said before,
you've always been one of my picks.
- That's right.
- Yeah, so…
That's why I wanted to talk to you today.
And…
- What is it?
- I don't know.
Anyway, my interest in you right now is…
Are you saying you're interested?
- You're my top pick right now.
- Oh, your top pick.
But like… I…
I don't want to confuse you
because I know that you have
feelings for Tae-hoon.
I don't want to interfere.
I must seem like a bit of a wimp, but…
I just really…
I don't think you're a wimp.
- Really?
- A wimp wouldn't call me out like this.
- You think so?
- A wimp can't do that.
The real wimp
is reading a book in his room.
Anyway, don't feel pressured.
Just know that's how I feel.
I just wanted to let you know.
So you just wanted me to know
you're interested in me?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Firstly, thank you.
- My pleasure. But honestly…
- Yeah?
I was so nervous before I went in.
- When you came in earlier?
- Yeah.
I was nervous and…
I also had butterflies.
Anyway, that's how I feel.
That's where I stand.
But how did you feel about our date today?
I was thankful.
I really appreciated it
because my top pick was also…
Not my top pick,
but for the first impression vote,
- I picked you too.
- Yeah.
I thought you seemed
like a really good guy.
I kept thinking to myself
that I would like to stay in touch
with you even after the show.
I'm glad that's how you saw me.
- Thank you for telling me.
- Yeah.
Honestly, I really appreciate it.
I had a lot on my mind and stuff,
but you've cheered me up.
Well, anyway…
Let's keep our chin up!
Yeah, let's stay strong!
- Thanks for telling me.
- Sure.
I'll give it some thought.
- I'll have a think.
- Okay.
- Thanks for telling me.
- Yeah.
Shall we get up now?
- Let's go.
- It's cold, right?
I'm not that cold.
- Really?
- I feel warmer now.
- Let's go.
- Yeah, let's go.
I feel so much lighter.
- Really?
- Yeah.
When I have something on my mind--
- You need to let it out?
- Yeah.
So I thought I'd try like this.
I was honestly so grateful
because I was feeling depressed
about how Tae-hoon acted.
That's why I cried.
So when Seung-hyun came
and told me all that,
I was so thankful.
It made me want to talk to him more.
I can't show her exactly what I'm feeling,
and I'm not sure
if I was fully successful,
but I think I managed
to convey my feelings to some degree.
She's my current top pick,
so I'll keep trying my best
to impress her.
- Just when she needed some comfort.
- Yeah.
Talk about perfect timing.
- He did great.
- It really cheered her up.
SH, don't cry.
- Don't cry.
- SH, don't cry.
- It's "either-or" questions.
- "Either-or."
I love it.
NORAEBANG
Shall we just go in order?
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
This is going to be challenging.
"What if your partner takes their coat off
for your friend on a cold day?"
That is f…
Freaking unacceptable.
Of course, it's unacceptable.
Han-ju nearly cursed.
I'd be cold too.
"I'd be cold too."
- Of course, it's not okay.
- Unacceptable.
Jung-yun, you're next.
"A partner who dated
just one person for ten years,
or someone who…"
- Gosh.
- I mean…
- 10 years?
- We haven't dated in 27 years.
This question isn't fair.
I think I prefer the former.
This one's a bit tricky.
It is tricky,
- but if I had to choose…
- Yeah.
What's this party of fun people?
I prefer the latter without a doubt.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But if they only dated
one person for ten years,
won't they keep thinking of their ex?
They're basically a divorcee.
She never holds back.
Do you want to join in?
No, keep going.
You all prefer the former?
Yeah. I prefer the former.
- That looks fun.
- Yeah, the former is a bit…
Go on. Pick one.
"Name a time when the person you like
made you upset."
The question is about the time
you've been upset by someone you like.
- She's right there listening.
- Yeah.
- By someone you like?
- Be honest.
- It has to be someone in the village.
Of course.
Upset by someone…
What if you've never been upset?
Should I make it up?
You haven't been hurt? Not even once?
Cross your heart?
- Why did you cry, then?
- Yeah, why?
There has to be a reason.
Can I step out for a minute?
Do you feel awkward?
So you have been upset.
She's running away.
- Why are you running away?
- She's running.
I would like to get a clear answer
from that person.
Now.
- In that case…
- We forgot to put the used ones aside.
I didn't think we'd get to me.
But it doesn't matter, does it?
If you get the same question…
"Name a time when the person you like
made you upset."
- It's the same question.
- Here it is.
It's the same thing again.
When they didn't like me back.
That is upsetting for sure.
It is upsetting.
Let's stack it like this.
- They've all experienced that.
- Yeah.
I was so busy thinking
about my own feelings.
I only worried about the person
I was interested in
and what I should do about it,
so I didn't think much
about the people around me.
But now that I have
organized my thoughts a bit,
I have a bit more headspace
to think about other people.
As a result of that,
I started noticing
Han-ju's expressions a bit more.
After all, she had told me
she was interested in me.
And I started wondering
what kind of things have hurt her, so…
Han-ju, can we talk for a bit?
- Yeah.
- I'd better give you guys space.
Jin-woo asked Han-ju to talk.
Where shall we go?
The Garden?
I just need a minute.
Okay.
I wanted to talk to you too.
I feel like Han-ju
may have gotten butterflies.
I had a lot to say,
but now I don't know where to start.
I wanted to thank you, firstly,
since you picked me for the dates.
And I've been feeling a little guilty.
For me,
you made the best impression
on the first day.
Don't make me mad.
I cried because of that.
So why did you have to read mine?
There were so many other diaries.
But it's just that…
On our date, you said I made
a great first impression on you.
So I thought maybe you liked me back.
But then,
it turned out I wasn't
your first impression pick.
Yeah, her name wasn't in his diary.
He didn't mention her once.
I feel like you'll get angrier
if I keep talking, so I'll stay quiet.
Come out with it, quickly.
What is it? Spill it.
Let's get it all out.
- You really want to talk it all out?
- Yeah.
I swear it's not that I wasn't interested.
- You know I had a hard few days.
- Yeah.
I honestly felt really torn
during that time.
Don't give me bullshit.
She's right. Don't give her bullshit.
Han-ju just got some closure,
- so he shouldn't give her hope again
- Yeah.
- if he's not interested.
- Right, exactly.
- It's better to leave her be.
- Yes.
Honestly, I really
gave it a lot of thought.
It was such a tough time for me.
I thought,
"He said he was into three women."
"But I guess
I'm not even in the top three."
- So…
- I swear you're mistaken.
You were definitely one of them.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I swear.
But anyway,
do you not have any regrets
or things you wish you did?
Regrets? Things I wish I did?
I do have a lot of regrets,
but in terms of doing something more…
I feel like I have been really honest, so…
You feel satisfied?
- I agree.
- In the past,
I always used to hide my feelings.
But since coming here,
I've been a bit too direct.
But it seemed so natural,
as if that's just your personality.
The way you speak too…
It didn't seem out of character for you.
After my date with you, I told the girls
that I came onto you quite aggressively.
But then two days later,
I was like, "He's not into me at all."
And so…
I embarrassed myself crying on TV
- because of you.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for a lot of things.
One of the things I feel
sorry about and regret is…
I know it's late,
but I'm finally starting to see you.
- He's noticing Han-ju?
- He is?
Does he finally see her charm?
- That's so great.
- Yeah.
This season is really… It's great.
So…
What? You little…
I'm sorry.
I've started noticing you
now that I have the headspace.
This is so annoying.
How am I supposed to take this?
Oh, man. What am I…
I don't know what I'm saying.
Anyway, yeah…
Anyway,
I don't know how big
your interest in me is, but…
You're the first person
to tell me I'm handsome.
- You are handsome.
- Thanks.
I really…
I appreciate it.
- It's cold, right? Shall we head back?
- Let's go.
Thanks for talking to me like this.
I realized I hadn't been
totally delusional,
so it made me think that maybe
I shouldn't give up hope just yet.
- Jin-woo seems interested in her.
- Yeah.
I think so too.
Because Jin-woo is getting
- a bit tired of waiting for Jeong-eun.
- He is.
But he's realizing now
that Han-ju's been really good to him,
and she's consistently
shown her interest in him.
But what I liked most about it was
that Han-ju was genuinely
happy and smiling.
- That's enough for me.
- Yeah.
But why are we seeing
so many new couples this close to the end?
- At this rate, our Ms. Popular,
- What's going to happen?
Su-ji, might end up alone…
It's looking that way.
…while everyone else happily couples up.
- Yeah.
- It's possible.
- We basically have two new couples.
- We do.
ETERNAL SINGLES' POST OFFICE
I'd better hurry and get her a gift.
A gift?
Is it this?
Tangerine card holder…
This is it.
I used my remaining gift coupons
on Hyun-seo.
- Yes. Use them all.
- Great.
- He used them on Hyun-seo. Good.
- It's all for her.
We played the Truth Game,
and one of the questions was…
- "Something you want from your top pick."
- "Something you want."
Something I want?
Give me the tangerine card holder
in the Post Office as a gift.
She gave an order.
She sounded like a boss.
She said she wanted to get
the tangerine card holder from someone.
So I ran to the Post Office
as soon as the group split up,
in case someone else got to it first.
I bought that first.
- That was close.
- He's in a rush.
In addition to it,
I wanted her to have
a memorabilia of Jeju Island.
There was a Jeju Island pen set,
so I got her that too,
along with a letter.
All done.
I used all my three coupons on her.
I wanted my gifts
to be sincere and meaningful,
so I only got gifts for her.
Well done, Hyuk-joon.
He's come back.
We thought you'd gone back to your room.
Oh, right.
- They all left to their rooms looking sad.
- How come?
We asked if they wanted to play Mafia,
but they said they were leaving
with sad voices.
We got rejected.
Check your cabinet.
- He's a funny guy.
- Hyun-seo's so calm.
He's funny.
Check your cabinet.
I was happy to get the card holder
since I'd said I wanted it.
It's cute.
He's like a well-trained puppy.
A puppy?
- Hyun-seo's quick to forget.
- Yes.
- She moves on quickly.
- Yeah.
They're compatible that way.
HAN SU-JI
AN JEONG-EUN
I wanted to tell someone so badly,
but since it's meant to be a secret…
She's in real trouble.
Yeah, Su-ji seems very troubled right now.
Did you have fun, at least?
My head is filled with thoughts.
Do you not regret not requesting a date?
I don't know.
But…
I don't feel like, "I wish I did it."
I just suddenly feel like
it might have been a good idea.
THIS MORNING
Will you request a date?
- I don't think so.
- Same.
Whatever. I'm not picking anyone.
She felt too conflicted.
Is there someone you wanted to pick
but didn't?
No, I really didn't want
to go on a date with anyone.
But I feel like I wasted a whole day.
- Did today feel a bit meaningless?
- Yeah.
- It makes sense you feel that way.
Maybe I should have
made better use of my time.
Maybe I should have picked someone.
A lot's on my mind because of that.
I don't know if it's because things
changed so much yesterday,
but I felt really conflicted this morning.
So I didn't want to go on any dates.
In the tangerine field this morning,
I didn't feel excited at all.
I felt really troubled
because there are only two days left.
And then…
I started thinking about Hyuk-joon.
He must have gone on a date
with someone else.
And I started to feel a bit regretful.
Maybe I should have just given it a shot.
Requesting a date isn't like
asking him to marry me.
So why did I make such a big deal of it?
It just weighed on my mind all day.
I thought, "Do I really like him?"
Then, when I got back to the village,
while I was sitting in the Lounge,
I found myself noticing
Hyuk-joon whenever he walked past.
I felt like this had to be
a sign that I was interested.
That must be why I noticed him
because I wasn't that bothered
about anyone else.
I noticed myself paying attention to him.
I just have a lot on my mind.
She should've requested
a date with Hyuk-joon.
That could've helped her figure out
her feelings more clearly.
I think that deep down,
Su-ji was probably hoping
Hyuk-joon might request a date with her.
I think she definitely did
because when you like someone,
you get your hopes up.
- That's true.
- So I think
she strongly hoped that Hyuk-joon
would request a date with her.
And that's what she probably meant
by leaving it up to fate.
Do you want to drop by the Post Office?
- Sure.
- I just want to quickly check
if I got anything.
Right now…
Up until now,
I felt like giving a gift was a big deal,
so I didn't want to give a gift to anyone.
But I kind of want to give
a gift as a lighthearted gesture.
She shouldn't think of it
as such a big deal.
He's checking if she took it.
She took it.
CHOI HYUK-JOON
He got something.
Wait, who is it from?
I got gloves.
Hold on.
No!
Who gave them?
Hyuk-joon is going to get swayed again.
A gift is a huge deal to him.
I think I'm just going to tell Hyuk-joon.
Tell him what?
That I don't know what this feeling is,
but I've been noticing him.
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Og Nam